https://www.machineseeker.com/privacy/#cookies

WATCH LIST
(0)
General
The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our
website.
Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the
subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below. You can edit your privacy settings for handling cookies at any time.
Data collection on our website
Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?
The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can
be
found in the website's required legal notice.
How do we collect your data?
Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact
form.
Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily
technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These
data
are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.
What do we use your data for?
Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to
analyze
how visitors use the site.
What rights do you have regarding your data?
You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the
purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or
deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further
questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the
competent regulatory authorities.
Analytics and third-party tools
When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily
using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be
able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain
tools.
Detailed information can be found in the following privacy policy.
You can object to this analysis. We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this
regard.
2. General information and mandatory information
Data protection
The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your
personal
data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy
policy.
If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data
with
which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what
we
use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.
Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security
breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.
Notice concerning the party responsible for this website
The party responsible for processing data on this website is:
Email: info@maschinensucher.de
The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes
and
means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).
Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data
Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at
any
time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we
receive your request may still be legally processed.
Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities
If there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the
competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection
legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered. A list
of
data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link: https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html
.
SSL or TLS encryption
This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of
confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an
encrypted
connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is
displayed in your browser's address bar.
If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.
Encrypted payments on this website
If you enter into a contract which requires you to send us your payment information (e.g. account number for
direct debits), we will require this data to process your payment.
Payment transactions using common means of payment (Visa/MasterCard, direct debit) are only made via
encrypted
SSL or TLS connections. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it
changes
from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon in your browser line is visible.
In the case of encrypted communication, any payment details you submit to us cannot be read by third
parties.
Information, blocking, deletion
As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any
of
your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been
processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at
any
time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal
data.
Opposition to promotional emails
We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice
requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The
website
operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email
spam, is received.
3. Data collection on our website
Cookies
Some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies
help
make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on
your
computer and saved by your browser.
Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit.
Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to
recognize
your browser when you next visit the site.
You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a
case-by-case
basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically
accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when
closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to
use
(such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website
operator
has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of
technical
errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be
treated separately in this privacy policy.
Server log files
The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits
to
us in "server log files". These are:
Browser type and browser version
Operating system used
Referrer URL
Host name of the accessing computer
Time of the server request
IP address
These data will not be combined with data from other sources.
The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a
contract
or for measures preliminary to a contract.
Contact form
Should you send us questions via the contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including
the
contact details you provide, to answer your question and any follow-up questions. We do not share this
information without your permission.
We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a)
DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The
data
processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
We will retain the data you provide on the contact form until you request its deletion, revoke your consent
for
its storage, or the purpose for its storage no longer pertains (e.g. after fulfilling your request). Any
mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain
unaffected
by this provision.
Registration on this website
You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here. The input data will
only be
used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory
information requested during registration must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your
registration.
To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we
will
use the email address specified during registration.
We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO. You
may
revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The
data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our
website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.
Processing of data (customer and contract data)
We collect, process, and use personal data only insofar as it is necessary to establish, or modify legal
relationships with us (master data). This is done based on Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing
of
data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract. We collect, process and use your
personal
data when accessing our website (usage data) only to the extent required to enable you to access our service
or
to bill you for the same.
Collected customer data shall be deleted after completion of the order or termination of the business
relationship. Legal retention periods remain unaffected.
Data transferred when signing up for services and digital content
We transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of
your contract with us, for example, to banks entrusted to process your payments.
Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do
so.
Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent.
The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a
contract
or for measures preliminary to a contract.
4. Social media
Facebook plugins (Like & Share buttons)
Our website includes plugins for the social network Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park,
California
94025, USA. The Facebook plugins can be recognized by the Facebook logo or the Like button on our site. For
an
overview of Facebook plugins, see https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/
.
When you visit our site, a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established via
the
plugin. This enables Facebook to receive information that you have visited our site from your IP address. If
you
click on the Facebook "Like button" while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the
content of
our site to your Facebook profile. This allows Facebook to associate visits to our site with your user
account.
Please note that, as the operator of this site, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted
to
Facebook or of how Facebook uses these data. For more information, please see Facebook's privacy policy at
https://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php
.
If you do not want Facebook to associate your visit to our site with your Facebook account, please log out of
your Facebook account.
Twitter plugin
Functions of the Twitter service have been integrated into our website and app. These features are offered by
Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. When you use Twitter and the
“Retweet”
function, the websites you visit are connected to your Twitter account and made known to other users. In
doing
so, data will also be transferred to Twitter. We would like to point out that, as the provider of these
pages,
we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by Twitter. For more
information on Twitter's privacy policy, please go to https://twitter.com/privacy
.
Your privacy preferences with Twitter can be modified in your account settings at https://twitter.com/account/settings
.
Instagram plugin
Our website contains functions of the Instagram service. These functions are offered by Instagram Inc., 1601
Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA.
If you are logged into your Instagram account, you can click the Instagram button to link the content of our
pages with your Instagram profile. This means that Instagram can associate visits to our pages with your
user
account. As the provider of this website, we expressly point out that we receive no information on the
content
of the transmitted data or its use by Instagram.
For more information, see the Instagram Privacy Policy: https://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/
.
LinkedIn plugin
Our site uses functions from the LinkedIn network. The service is provided by LinkedIn Corporation, 2029
Stierlin
Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
Each time one of our pages containing LinkedIn features is accessed, your browser establishes a direct
connection
to the LinkedIn servers. LinkedIn is informed that you have visited our web pages from your IP address. If
you
use the LinkedIn “Recommend” button and are logged into your LinkedIn account, it is possible
for
LinkedIn to associate your visit to our website to your user account. We would like to point out that, as
the
provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used
by
LinkedIn.
More information can be found in the LinkedIn privacy policy at https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
.
XING Plugin
Our website uses features provided by the XING network. The provider is XING AG, Dammtorstraße 29-32,
20354
Hamburg, Germany.
Each time one of our pages containing XING features is accessed, your browser establishes a direct connection
to
the XING servers. To the best of our knowledge, no personal data is stored in the process. In particular, no
IP
addresses are stored nor is usage behavior evaluated.
For more information about data protection and the XING Share button, please see the XING privacy policy at
https://www.xing.com/app/share?op=data_protection
.
Pinterest plugin
Our website contains functions of the Pinterest social network, operated by Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street,
Palo
Alto, CA, 94301, USA.
When you visit a page containing the Pinterest social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to
the
Pinterest servers. The plugin transmits this log data to Pinterest servers in the United States. This log
data
may include your IP address, the address of the websites visited, which also includes Pinterest features,
browser type and settings, the date and time of the request, how you use Pinterest, and cookies.
More information about the purpose, scope and further processing and use of data by Pinterest, as well as
your
rights and options to protect your privacy, can be found in the privacy notices of Pinterest: https://about.pinterest.com/de/privacy-policy
.
5. Analytics and advertising
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre
Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and that
allow
an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this
website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.
Google Analytics cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate
interest
in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising.
IP anonymization
We have activated the IP anonymization feature on this website. Your IP address will be shortened by Google
within the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to
transmission
to the United States. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a Google server in the US and
shortened there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website to evaluate your
use
of the website, to compile reports on website activity, and to provide other services regarding website
activity
and Internet usage for the website operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google
Analytics will not be merged with any other data held by Google.
Browser plugin
You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we
wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this
website.
You can also prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the website (incl. your IP address)
from
being passed to Google, and the processing of these data by Google, by downloading and installing the
browser
plugin available at the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
.
Objecting to the collection of data
You can prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. An opt-out
cookie will be set to prevent your data from being collected on future visits to this site: Disable
Google
Analytics.
For more information about how Google Analytics handles user data, see Google's privacy policy: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en
.
Outsourced data processing
We have entered into an agreement with Google for the outsourcing of our data processing and fully implement
the
strict requirements of the German data protection authorities when using Google Analytics.
Demographic data collection by Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics' demographic features. This allows reports to be generated containing
statements about the age, gender, and interests of site visitors. This data comes from interest-based
advertising from Google and third-party visitor data. This collected data cannot be attributed to any
specific
individual person. You can disable this feature at any time by adjusting the ads settings in your Google
account
or you can forbid the collection of your data by Google Analytics as described in the section "Refusal of
data
collection".
Google Analytics Remarketing
Our websites use the features of Google Analytics Remarketing combined with the cross-device capabilities of
Google Ads and DoubleClick. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain
View, CA 94043, USA.
This feature makes it possible to link target audiences for promotional marketing created with Google
Analytics
Remarketing to the cross-device capabilities of Google Ads and Google DoubleClick. This allows
advertising
to be displayed based on your personal interests, identified based on your previous usage and surfing
behavior
on one device (e.g. your mobile phone), on other devices (such as a tablet or computer).
Once you have given your consent, Google will associate your web and app browsing history with your Google
Account for this purpose. That way, any device that signs in to your Google Account can use the same
personalized promotional messaging.
To support this feature, Google Analytics collects Google-authenticated IDs of users that are temporarily
linked
to our Google Analytics data to define and create audiences for cross-device ad promotion.
You can permanently opt out of cross-device remarketing/targeting by turning off personalized advertising in
your
Google Account; follow this link: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/
.
The aggregation of the data collected in your Google Account data is based solely on your consent, which you
may
give or withdraw from Google per Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO. For data collection operations not merged into your
Google Account (for example, because you do not have a Google Account or have objected to the merge), the
collection of data is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in
analyzing
anonymous user behavior for promotional purposes.
For more information and the Google Privacy Policy, go to: https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/
.
Google Ads and Google Conversion Tracking
This website uses Google Ads. Ads is an online advertising program from Google Inc., 1600
Amphitheater
Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google").
As part of Google Ads, we use so-called conversion tracking. When you click on an ad served by Google, a
conversion tracking cookie is set. Cookies are small text files that your internet browser stores on your
computer. These cookies expire after 30 days and are not used for personal identification of the user.
Should
the user visit certain pages of the website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and the website can
tell
that the user clicked on the ad and proceeded to that page.
Each Google Ads advertiser has a different cookie. Thus, cookies cannot be tracked using the website of
an
Ads advertiser. The information obtained using the conversion cookie is used to create conversion
statistics
for the Ads advertisers who have opted for conversion tracking. Customers are told the total number of
users
who clicked on their ad and were redirected to a conversion tracking tag page. However, advertisers do not
obtain any information that can be used to personally identify users. If you do not want to participate in
tracking, you can opt-out of this by easily disabling the Google Conversion Tracking cookie by changing your
browser settings. In doing so, you will not be included in the conversion tracking statistics.
Conversion cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest
in
analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising.
For more information about Google Ads and Google Conversion Tracking, see the Google Privacy Policy: https://www.google.de/policies/privacy/
.
You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a
case-by-case
basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically
accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when
closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
Google reCAPTCHA
We use "Google reCAPTCHA" (hereinafter "reCAPTCHA") on our websites. This service is provided by Google Inc.,
1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").
reCAPTCHA is used to check whether the data entered on our website (such as on a contact form) has been
entered
by a human or by an automated program. To do this, reCAPTCHA analyzes the behavior of the website visitor
based
on various characteristics. This analysis starts automatically as soon as the website visitor enters the
website. For the analysis, reCAPTCHA evaluates various information (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor
has
been on the website, or mouse movements made by the user). The data collected during the analysis will be
forwarded to Google.
The reCAPTCHA analyses take place completely in the background. Website visitors are not advised that such an
analysis is taking place.
Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in
protecting
its site from abusive automated crawling and spam.
For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google's privacy policy, please visit the following links: https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/
and https://www.google.com/recaptcha/intro/android.html
.
Facebook Pixel
Our website measures conversions using visitor action pixels from Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California
Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook").
These allow the behavior of site visitors to be tracked after they click on a Facebook ad to reach the
provider's
website. This allows an analysis of the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market
research purposes and their future optimization.
The data collected is anonymous to us as operators of this website and we cannot use it to draw any
conclusions
about our users' identities. However, the data are stored and processed by Facebook, which may make a
connection
to your Facebook profile and which may use the data for its own advertising purposes, as stipulated in the
Facebook privacy policy
. This
will
allow Facebook to display ads both on Facebook and on third-party sites. We have no control over how this
data
is used.
Check out Facebook's privacy policy to learn more about protecting your privacy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
.
You can also deactivate the custom audiences remarketing feature in the Ads Settings section at https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen
. You will first need to log into Facebook.
If you do not have a Facebook account, you can opt out of usage-based advertising from Facebook on the
website of
the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/praferenzmanagement/
.
Criteo
Our platform uses technology from Criteo GmbH (Gewürzmühlstr. 11, 80538 Munich; "Criteo") to collect information
about your user behavior for marketing purposes in a purely anonymous form and to set cookies for this purpose.
This enables Criteo to analyze your user behavior and subsequently display targeted product recommendations as
appropriate advertising banners when you visit other websites. Under no circumstances can the anonymous data be
used to identify you personally. The information collected by Criteo is used only to improve the advertising
offering.
For more information about privacy, please visit https://www.criteo.com/de/privacy/.
You may opt out of the use of this Site by clicking here: https://www.criteo.com/de/privacy/.
Hubspot
Our platform uses technology from HubSpot Germany GmbH (Koppenstraße 93, 10243 Berlin, Germany, "Hubspot") to collect information about your user behavior for marketing purposes and to set cookies for this purpose. Hubspot may analyze your user behavior and then display targeted product recommendations as appropriate advertising banners when you visit other websites. Hubspot will use the information it collects only to improve its advertising offering. For more information about privacy, please visit https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy. You may opt-out of this service by clicking here: https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy.
We also use Hubspot as a service provider to process data to maintain customer relationships and relationships with prospective customers ("Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"). We may use it to transfer personal customer information (first name, last name, company name, phone number, e-mail address, customer number, contact history) to Hubspot Inc. (25 First Street, Cambridge, MA 02141 USA). Hubspot is certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield. Further information can be found here: https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy.
Outbrain
On our platform information about your user behaviour is collected by the technology of Outbrain UK Limited (5th Floor, The Place, 175 High Holborn, London, WC1V 7AA, UVereinigtes Königreich, "Outbrain") for marketing purposes in purely anonymous form and cookies are set for this purpose. This allows Outbrain to analyse your user behaviour and then display targeted product recommendations as appropriate banner ads when you visit other websites. Under no circumstances can the anonymous data be used to identify you personally. The information collected by Outbrain is only used to improve the advertising offer.
For more information about privacy, please visit https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#privacy-policy. The option to opt out can be found here: https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#the_site.
Inspectlet
On our platform, the technology of Inspectlet Inc (Santa Clara, CA, USA, "Inspeclet") is used to collect information about your user behaviour for the purpose of optimising the platform in a purely anonymous form and to set cookies for this purpose. Under no circumstances can the anonymous data be used to identify you personally. The data collected by Inspeclet is only used to improve the website.
Data collected by Inspectlet may be transferred to an Inspectlet server in the USA. In the event of such a transfer of data, we will ensure that Inspectlet guarantees a level of protection in accordance with the data protection regulations in the EU, in accordance with Art. 44 et seq. of the DSGVO; in all other respects, the transfer of data takes place on the basis of Art. 28 DSGVO.
Further information on data protection can be found here: https://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy. You can find the option to opt out here: https: //www.inspectlet.com/optout
Microsoft Clarity
On our platform, the technology of Microsoft Corporation (One Microsoft Way, Redmond, WA 98052-6399, USA, "Microsoft") is used to collect information about your user behavior in a purely anonymous form for the purpose of platform optimization and cookies are set for this purpose. Under no circumstances can the anonymous data be used to identify you personally. The data collected by Microsoft is only used to improve the website. Data collected by Microsoft may be transferred to a Microsoft server in the USA. In the event of such a transfer of data, we will ensure that Microsoft provides a level of protection of your personal data that is adequate for data protection in the EU in accordance with Art. 44 et seq. GDPR; in all other respects the data transfer is based on Art. 28 GDPR.
Further information on data protection can be found here:
https://privacy.microsoft.com/privacystatement
6. Newsletter
Newsletter data
If you would like to receive our newsletter, we require a valid email address as well as information that
allows
us to verify that you are the owner of the specified email address and that you agree to receive this
newsletter. No additional data is collected or is only collected on a voluntary basis. We only use this data
to
send the requested information and do not pass it on to third parties.
We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)
(a)
DSGVO. You can revoke consent to the storage of your data and email address as well as their use for sending
the
newsletter at any time, e.g. through the "unsubscribe" link in the newsletter. The data processed before we
receive your request may still be legally processed.
The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you
cancel
your subscription when said data will be deleted. Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. email
addresses
for the members area) remain unaffected.
MailChimp
This website uses the services of MailChimp to send newsletters. This service is provided by Rocket Science
Group
LLC, 675 Ponce De Leon Ave NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA.
MailChimp is a service which organizes and analyzes the distribution of newsletters. If you provide data
(e.g.
your email address) to subscribe to our newsletter, it will be stored on MailChimp servers in the USA.
MailChimp is certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield. The Privacy Shield is an agreement between the
European
Union (EU) and the US to ensure compliance with European privacy standards in the United States.
We use MailChimp to analyze our newsletter campaigns. When you open an email sent by MailChimp, a file
included
in the email (called a web beacon) connects to MailChimp's servers in the United States. This allows us to
determine if a newsletter message has been opened and which links you click on. In addition, technical
information is collected (e.g. time of retrieval, IP address, browser type, and operating system). This
information cannot be assigned to a specific recipient. It is used exclusively for the statistical analysis
of
our newsletter campaigns. The results of these analyses can be used to better tailor future newsletters to
your
interests.
If you do not want your usage of the newsletter to be analyzed by MailChimp, you will have to unsubscribe
from
the newsletter. For this purpose, we provide a link in every newsletter we send. You can also unsubscribe
from
the newsletter directly on the website.
Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time by unsubscribing to
the
newsletter. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you
cancel
your subscription when said data will be deleted from our servers and those of MailChimp. Data we have
stored
for other purposes (e.g. email addresses for the members area) remains unaffected.
For details, see the MailChimp privacy policy at https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/
.
Completion of a data processing agreement
We have entered into a data processing agreement with MailChimp, in which we require MailChimp to protect the
data of our customers and not to disclose said data to third parties. This agreement may be viewed at the
following link: https://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/data-processing-agreement/sample-agreement/
.
7. Plugins and tools
YouTube
Our website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC,
901
Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA.
If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established.
Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited.
If you're logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly
with
your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account.
YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6
(1)
(f) DSGVO.
Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube
under https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy
.
Vimeo
Our website uses features provided by the Vimeo video portal. This service is provided by Vimeo Inc., 555
West
18th Street, New York, New York 10011, USA.
If you visit one of our pages featuring a Vimeo plugin, a connection to the Vimeo servers is established.
Here
the Vimeo server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Vimeo will receive your
IP
address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Vimeo when you visit our website or do not have a
Vimeo
account. The information is transmitted to a Vimeo server in the US, where it is stored.
If you are logged in to your Vimeo account, Vimeo allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly
with
your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Vimeo account.
For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Vimeo Privacy Policy at https://vimeo.com/privacy
.
Google Web Fonts
For uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your
browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.
For this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to Google servers. Google thus becomes
aware
that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a
uniform and attractive presentation of our website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6
(1)
(f) DSGVO.
If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer.
Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq
and in Google's privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
.
Google Maps
This site uses the Google Maps map service via an API. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre
Parkway,
Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
To use Google Maps, it is necessary to save your IP address. This information is generally transmitted to a
Google server in the USA and stored there. The provider of this site has no influence on this data
transfer.
The use of Google Maps is in the interest of making our website appealing and to facilitate the location of
places specified by us on the website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f)
DSGVO.
Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of Google at https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/
.
Sparkpost
This website uses the services of Sparkpost for the distribution of newsletters. Provider is Sparkpost Message Systems, Inc. 9130 Guilford Road Columbia, MD 21046 USA.
Sparkpost is a service that enables the organization and analysis of platform emails and newsletters. If you enter data for the purpose of using our platform (e.g. e-mail address), this data is stored on Sparkpost's servers in the EU.
With the help of Sparkpost, we can analyze the e-mails we send. When you open an e-mail sent with Sparkpost, a file contained in the e-mail (so-called web-beacon) connects to the Sparkpost servers. This allows us to determine whether a message has been opened and which links have been clicked on, if any. Furthermore, technical information is collected (e.g. time of retrieval, IP address, browser type and operating system). This information is used exclusively for statistical analysis. The results of these analyses can be used to better adapt future e-mails to the interests of the recipients.
If you do not wish to receive analyses from Sparkpost, you will have to unsubscribe. For this purpose, we provide a corresponding link in each message. Furthermore, you can also unsubscribe directly on the website.
The data processing is based on your consent and/or the fulfilment of contractual claims (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a/b GDPR). You can revoke this consent at any time by unsubscribing from the newsletter. The legality of the data processing operations that have already taken place remains unaffected by the revocation.
For further details, please refer to Sparkpost's data protection regulations at:
https://www.sparkpost.com/policies/privacy/
Twilio
This website uses Twilio, a service tool of Twilio Ireland Limited, 25-28 North Wall Quay, Dublin 1, Ireland, to improve customer communication. The data (especially your mobile phone number) is only exchanged encrypted between Twilio and Machineseeker.com.
The main goal is to provide our customers with a secure authentication and information process on the platform. For example, we can use SMS messages to inform our customers even faster about changes in the customer account.
The data processing is based on the fulfilment of contractual claims (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a/b GDPR). You can find more details in the Twilio data protection regulations at:
https://www.twilio.com/legal/privacy
Simple Fax
This website uses Simple Fax, a service tool of simple Communication GmbH, Salzdahlumer Str. 196, 38126 Braunschweig, Germany, to improve customer communication. The data (especially your fax number) is only exchanged in encrypted form between Simple Fax and Machineseeker.com.
This is especially important for sending important documents such as invoices to our customers.
The data processing is based on the fulfilment of contractual claims (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a/b GDPR). You can find more details in the data protection regulations of Simple Fax at:
https://simple-fax.de/datenschutzerklaerung
eBrief
This website uses eBrief, an offer from PIN AG, Alt-Moabit 91, 10559 Berlin, Germany, to improve customer communication. The data (especially your address) is only exchanged between eBrief and Machineseeker.com in encrypted form.
This is especially important for sending important documents such as invoices to our customers.
Data processing is based on the fulfilment of contractual claims (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a/b DSGVO). For further details, please refer to the data protection regulations of eBrief at:
https://www.ebrief.de/datenschutz
8. Payment service providers
PayPal
Our website accepts payments via PayPal. The provider of this service is PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l &
Cie,
S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg.
If you select payment via PayPal, the payment data you provide will be supplied to PayPal based on Art. 6 (1)
(a)
(Consent) and Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO (Processing for contract purposes). You have the option to revoke your
consent at any time with future effect. It does not affect the processing of data previously collected.
Adyen
On our website we offer payment via Adyen among other things. The provider of this payment service is Adyen BV, Simon Carmiggelstraat 6 - 50, 1011 DJ Amsterdam, The Netherlands (hereinafter "Adyen").
If you choose payment via Adyen, the payment data you enter will be transmitted to Adyen.
The transmission of your data to Adyen is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a DSGVO (consent) and Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO (processing for the fulfilment of a contract). You have the possibility to revoke your consent to data processing at any time. Revocation does not affect the effectiveness of data processing operations carried out in the past.
Mangopay
On our website we offer payment via Mangopay among other things. The provider of this payment service is MANGOPAY SA, 2 Avenue Amélie, L-1125 Luxembourg (hereinafter "Mangopay").
If you choose payment via Mangopay, the payment data you enter will be transmitted to Mangopay.
The transmission of your data to Mangopay is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a DSGVO (consent) and Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO (processing for the fulfilment of a contract). You have the possibility to revoke your consent to data processing at any time. Revocation does not affect the effectiveness of data processing operations carried out in the past.
Try our app for used machines now!
Machineseeker app for iPhone and Android.
More information
Machineseeker.com is official sponsor of:
Popular used machines:
Well-known manufacturers:
A-Z
All information, offers and prices on this site are subject to change and non-binding!
By using this website, you acknowledge and agree to our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Statement.
Designated trademarks belong to their respective holders.
Machineseeker Group GmbH does not accept any liability for the content of linked websites.
© 1999-2020
Machineseeker Group GmbH
